This is now a antibacterial
satellite or a chemical in the world.
ten, ten, ten, ten, ten,
Thank you.
Let's go.
I don't know.
Satsang with Mooji
Wait a minute.
Who are you guys?
Stay away from me. Damn it.
Oh, for Pete's sake.
What a mess that was.
Surrounded by that lot, I wondered
what was going to happen to us.
Back there, it sounded like many
of them were saying Bakshish.
What do you suppose that means?
It means, give me money.
I should have known that.
What a backward little
hellhole this place is. My God!
Polnareff,
once you get used to it, you'll understand
the good things about this country.
I'd never get used to a place like this.
But this chai, or whatever you called
it, this is actually fairly decent stuff.
I think it's a pretty interesting country.
I really kind of like it.
Jotaro, do you really mean that?
How can you say that with a straight face?
They say once you live in
a place, it grows on you.
I don't get it.
You Asian guys must lack any sense of beauty
or elegance to like a place like this.
Whatever.
I'm gonna go take a shit.
What a vulgar man!
Oh.
Our dishes have arrived.
Ah.
And they look delicious.
Just as I would expect
from a tourist cafe.
A clean bathroom.
Hmm.
India getting close.
Huh?
You are...
What?!
No one there.
Did I imagine it?
I'm sure I saw some strange guy
outside the window just now.
What?
No way!
What is he?
Why can I only see him in the mirror?
That guy!
A right hand!
Not good!
Oh no you don't!
Silver Chariot!
Goddamn shit!
Where is he?
Where did he disappear to?
Now, where is the main body of that stand?
God damn it!
I'll never find him in a
crowded place like this!
What happened, Polnareff?
At last, I found him. It's him.
The bastard who killed my sister.
I finally found him.
Now, just hold on, Polnareff.
I understand how you feel, but calm down.
It could be an enemy trap.
Wait, you say?
You say you understand my feelings?
I must say you impress me, Avdol. What?
My younger sister and I, we lost
our parents at an early age.
We tried our best to get by
all on our own after that.
Then my sister was brutally
violated and murdered!
These feelings of mine...
You'd have to live through
that to ever understand them!
That's the only way!
Mr. Joestar,
I'm sorry, but it's time I part ways with
all of you and continue my journey alone.
What do you mean by that, Polnareff? Hmm?
Now that I know my sister's
assailant is somewhere close by,
I can't rest easy until I find him.
Even though you don't know his face
or the true nature of his stand?
I know both of his hands are right
hands, and that's good enough for me.
They say the tomb robber
becomes the mummy.
What do you mean by that?
Now just a minute.
You think that this guy
is going to defeat me?
I'm saying it's dangerous.
You'd be all alone
against an unknown stand.
So, Avdol,
I heard that when you met
Dio for the first time,
you were so frightened that you ran away.
What is that you say?
I've been alone from the beginning.
I have fought all of my
battles alone, until now.
Listen up!
I'll make this perfectly clear.
First of all, I don't care
about that guy Dio one bit.
I believe I told you that I was only coming
along with you to seek my own vengeance.
Paul Naref, don't try to stop him, Avdol.
Yes, but Mr. Joestar...
It's all right. Let him go.
As expected, Mr.
Joestar, you're very understanding.
Well, see ya.
Well, looks like we'd gone and provoked
that boy, didn't we, Mr. J. Kyle?
It's you.
What happened to you
yesterday I waited such a long
time hold your horses did
I promise I'd be there
no oh no please I want
to stay with you for the
rest of my life stop talking
crazy like hell you just
barely turned 16 girl I'm
old enough to marry and
I love you with all my
heart hey I'm just a drifter
I got no home I live this
whole life day to day
and in the end I'm destined
to die on the street.
Listen to me.
You come from one of them
aristocratic families.
You shouldn't be thinking about
marrying old cowboy like me,
even though we love each other
so very, very much, you see.
Is that true?
Can you say that you love me more
than anyone else in the whole world?
You bet.
More than anyone else
in a whole wide world.
So you see.
It's because I love you
so much I can't marry you.
You understand, don't you?
Oh, darn, this is so
heartbreakingly difficult for me.
Oh, yes?
I'll hold you like this from time to time.
That's good enough for me.
All right.
Well, you best run on home.
Your parents be worried about you.
Yes, I'd better be going.
Well, that was damn annoying.
You're probably thinking I'm
just complicating things again.
But it's mighty damn convenient to have
that kind of woman all over the world.
They'll do anything for you.
Even sacrifice their lives.
You already know the way I like to
do things, don't you, Mr. J. Guile?
Well, just as we expected,
Polnarev's gone off by his self.
Reckon we ought to go
kill him now or what?
Yeah.
Hey there.
Listen up, partner.
Somebody asks you if you've seen a
man whose hands are both right hands.
Send him over towards
the outskirts of town.
Yes, yes, of course, Kainzor.
Step one completed.
Have you seen a man whose
hands are both right hands?
Eh, I don't know.
Thanks a lot.
Everything is ready, partner.
Now we just wait for the
prey to step into our trap.
Oh, my God.
Well, now.
Shall we hit the trail?
You know, with your stand, the hanged
man and mind the emperor being partners,
we can kill them all.
I was able to find some transportation.
We can leave whenever you're ready.
Right.
Shall we get underway?
Avdol-san, what's...
What's wrong, then?
Mr. Joestar,
doesn't it seem strange
that our enemy waited
until Polnareff was alone
before showing himself?
I cannot help it.
My instincts keep telling me that this
was just a ploy to lure him away from us.
Frankly, I feel exactly
the same way myself, Avdol.
And we can't just leave things like this
when our comrade might be in danger!
And so, let's get in the truck now.
And find him?
What's that?
You say you've seen him?
Uh, yes.
You're sure you saw him?
A man whose hands are
both right hands. Well?
Now, where is he?
On the street, over there.
So he is here, at last.
Oh, shit.
This traffic is backed up solid.
We're not going to make any
progress at all at this rate.
He couldn't have gotten too far, so
let's split up and search for him.
We'll take this direction.
Kakyoin, stay with the truck. All right.
This guy.
The gun is mightier than the sword.
Now that's a fine saying, ain't it?
No, it's not him.
Hey, just who the hell are you, huh?
Name's Hull Horse, and I control the
stand that's known as the Emperor.
I don't give a damn
about you or your stand.
I'm looking for a man whose
hands are both right hands.
Huh, what a rude fella.
You asked, so I introduced myself.
Hell, never mind.
If you're looking for my partner,
he's around here somewhere.
What?
Where?
Where is he?
Hey, I don't have a lot of time to
waste on a little shit like you.
Where is he, huh?
Hehehe!
Hey, you.
What's so funny?
Know what Lord Dio told me?
That guy Polnareff has a habit
of underestimating his enemies,
so it's easy to whoop him.
It really is true, so I just had to laugh.
What?
If you're saying I have to beat you to get
to him, well then you give me no choice.
...but to grant your wish.
It cannot be.
Do not do anything rash, Polnareff.
No need to rush things.
Hey, Polnareff, you ever heard of
that game called Soldier's Chess?
Soldier's Chess?
The tank is stronger than the
soldier, but weaker than the mine.
Anyway, it's a game based on the
fundamental principles of battle and such.
In the case of Whole Horses
Emperor and you, well,
the rules of Soldier's Tests
apply perfectly, you see.
That is, the gun's mightier
than the sword, my friend.
Look, just what the hell are
you trying to get at anyway?
You see, my stand is the gun,
so your sword can't beat my gun.
What's that?
I can beat your bum?
Oh, you're into that stuff!
You...
I'll fucking kill you!
You underestimated me,
Polnareff. You lose.
You think I can't strike
down a bullet like that?
Piece of cake!
Silver, cheerio!
What?
It can't be!
It changed directions!
Even the bullet is part of my stand.
Now I gotcha.
You didn't expect that, did ya?
Now you're gonna die!
What the...
Abdul!
I was worried, so I came looking for you.
You worried about me?
The enemy knows everything
there is to know about us.
You said you had battled alone until now.
But from now on, you cannot win alone.
Why, you?
Are you still lecturing me?
Well, well.
You picked a hell of a time to
interfere with our showdown.
See?
Out of the way, Polnareff.
The bullet, it is returning.
He is able to control
the path of this bullet.
You can avoid a sword,
but what about this?
I'll burn it away. Magicians!
Abdo-san!
Hey, the bullet!
Andrew-san!
Old man!
What's the matter, Shotaro?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Whoa, now this is fortunate.
You see, my gun and J.
Giles' mirror, they just don't
get along with Abdel's fire.
Yes, they're very lucky.
For us, there are no more pieces to
worry about in this soldier's chest.
Oh, Abdel, sir.
It can't be.
Wake up, Avdol-san.
Open your eyes, please.
How pathetic.
You like to lecture others so
much and just look what happened.
What did you say, Polnareff?
Because he tried to save you.
Avdol-san is...
Who asked him to save me?
What a nosy meddler, always lecturing me.
A guy like him gets to be a drag.
That's why I told you that
I wanted to do this alone.
Polnareff, I can't believe I'm
hearing this from you right now.
It's so damned annoying.
For someone to die right before my eyes
like that, that is so goddamned annoying!
Thank you.
Let's go.